{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Steel Beam Fabrication Contractors","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/40431/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40431,"taskName":"Steel Beams (Custom) - Fabricate","taskDescription":"Fabricate Custom Steel Beams","xmTaskDescriptor":"Steel Beam Fabrication Contractors","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":234,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Steel Beams Custom colored wall","textMessagingName":"Make Steel Beams","rolloverLongDesc":"These are the firms that create custom beams to order. Often, they are not the firms who actually install the beams. See separate category for repairing structural problems.","rolloverShortDesc":"Create beams to specifications","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Fabricate Custom Steel Beams.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Steel Beam Fabrication \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | I Beam Fabricators","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":51,"acceptGoal":4,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Steel Beam Fabrication","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Steel Beams (Custom) - Fabricate","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Steel Beam Project","urlName":"Steel-Beams-Custom-Fabricate","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Steel Beam Fabrication Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor","searchKeywords":"Steel,Beams,Custom,colored,wall,working,structure,metal,stamped,concrete,Fabricate","emcCategoryOid":-12049,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":722,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40431/":{"taskOID":40431,"originalTaskOID":40431,"setID":722,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":4520,"questionDisplayText":"What Beam Supports","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What will the beam be supporting?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1839,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Deck","answerDisplayText":"Deck","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5412,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Roof structure only","answerDisplayText":"Roof structure only","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5390,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Roof and one floor above","answerDisplayText":"Roof and one floor above","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5391,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Roof and two floors above","answerDisplayText":"Roof and two floors above","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4521,"questionDisplayText":"Where Beam Used","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Where is the beam being used?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":587,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Above doorway or window opening","answerDisplayText":"Above doorway or window opening","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":588,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Above garage door opening","answerDisplayText":"Above garage door opening","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":874,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"At fireplace opening","answerDisplayText":"At fireplace opening","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6206,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Supporting hot tub on a deck","answerDisplayText":"Supporting hot tub on a deck","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6205,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Supporting floor structure","answerDisplayText":"Supporting floor structure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3161,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"In place of a load-bearing wall","answerDisplayText":"In place of a load-bearing wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4522,"questionDisplayText":"Deliver beam?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Would you like the beam delivered to the job site?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":4520,"questionDisplayText":"What Beam Supports","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What will the beam be supporting?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1839,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Deck","answerDisplayText":"Deck","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5412,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Roof structure only","answerDisplayText":"Roof structure only","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5390,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Roof and one floor above","answerDisplayText":"Roof and one floor above","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5391,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Roof and two floors above","answerDisplayText":"Roof and two floors above","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":1839,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Deck","answerDisplayText":"Deck","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5412,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Roof structure only","answerDisplayText":"Roof structure only","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5390,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Roof and one floor above","answerDisplayText":"Roof and one floor above","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5391,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Roof and two floors above","answerDisplayText":"Roof and two floors above","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4521,"questionDisplayText":"Where Beam Used","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Where is the beam being used?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":587,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Above doorway or window opening","answerDisplayText":"Above doorway or window opening","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":588,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Above garage door opening","answerDisplayText":"Above garage door opening","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":874,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"At fireplace opening","answerDisplayText":"At fireplace opening","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6206,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Supporting hot tub on a deck","answerDisplayText":"Supporting hot tub on a deck","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6205,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Supporting floor structure","answerDisplayText":"Supporting floor structure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3161,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"In place of a load-bearing wall","answerDisplayText":"In place of a load-bearing wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":587,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Above doorway or window opening","answerDisplayText":"Above doorway or window opening","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":588,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Above garage door opening","answerDisplayText":"Above garage door opening","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":874,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"At fireplace opening","answerDisplayText":"At fireplace opening","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6206,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Supporting hot tub on a deck","answerDisplayText":"Supporting hot tub on a deck","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6205,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Supporting floor structure","answerDisplayText":"Supporting floor structure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3161,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"In place of a load-bearing wall","answerDisplayText":"In place of a load-bearing wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4522,"questionDisplayText":"Deliver beam?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Would you like the beam delivered to the job site?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]}}